export const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
    answers: ["45", "90", "60"],
    correct: "90",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
    answers: ["obtuse", "acute", "right angled"],
    correct: "right angled",
  },
  {
    question: "A triangle can have",
    answers: ["one right angle", "two right angles"],
    correct: "one right angle",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following can form a right angled triangle?",
    answers: ["14, 15, 26", "12, 16, 20", "none"],
    correct: "none",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following triangles are always similar?",
    answers: ["Equilateral triangle", "Isosceles triangle"],
    correct: "Equilateral triangle",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If one angle of a triangle is obtuse, then which one of the following is the possible measure of remaining angles?",
    answers: ["100", "85"],
    correct: "85",
  },
  {
    question:
      "If the largest angle in a triangle is 70°, what is the least possible value of the smallest angle of the triangle?",
    answers: ["30", "10"],
    correct: "10",
  },
  {
    question: "The perimeter of scalene triangle with sides a, b, c is",
    answers: ["a + b + c", "2a", "None of these"],
    correct: "a + b + c",
  },
  {
    question: "A scalene triangle has ___ lines of symmetry",
    answers: ["two", "no", "15"],
    correct: "no",
  },
  {
    question:
      "There is a right triangle PQR where: angle Q = 90°; angle P = angle R. What is the measure of angles P and R?",
    answers: ["85", "65", "45"],
    correct: "45",
  },
];
